<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gbaranski</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on gbaranski</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About me High school student. Open-source enthusiast, full stack experience with different kind of applications, my Github Profile.
Contact Github: gbaranski
Email: root@gbaranski.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating ncurses-like TUI Applications in Rust using Cursive</title>
      <link>/posts/rust-tui/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rust-tui/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A post describing creating a TUI application in Rust for the Houseflow project. It enables triggering events, like turning on lights, on connected IoT devices.
Goal The goal of this project is to create something similar to ncspot, a Spotify client in CLI that uses the cursive.
Getting started The first step is to initialize an empty project
cargo new --bin rust-blog-tui This will create a directory with the given name and few files inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>My projects All of them are available on my Github profile
Houseflow Home automation platform, the project in which I put the most effort. Started it at the very beginning of the programming journey. This project involves a lot of different topics, like networking, electronics, mobile and web development, databases, devops, etc.
Made using
 Rust for high performance networking services with low memory footprint. My plan is to run that on cheap Raspberry Pi.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
